Guide to the New York State Farm Bureau Federation records, [ca. 1918-1968]
New York State Farm Bureau Federation records
- Potato Marketing Programs, 1961-62 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Grade Changes Certrified Seed Potatoes, 1958-59 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Potato Red Label Program, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Proposed Changes Potato Grades, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Potato Promotion, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Potato Conference, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Potato Club Reorganization, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Potato Study Committee, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Potato Research (Golden Nematode), 1958 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- Potato Meeting - Boston, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Potatoes - Nutritive Value, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- Potato Diversion - Study and Programs, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- Potato Supports - Controls, Etc., 1960 (Box 39, Folder 51)
- American Farm Bureau Federation (AFBF) Columbus Apple Conference, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 52)
- American Farm Bureau Federation (AFBF) Columbus Apple Conference, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 53)
- Great Lakes Cooperative, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 54)
- Controlled Atmosphere Storage Operators, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 55)
- Hail Suppression, 1956-58 (Box 39, Folder 56)
- Export Foods, Inc., a New York Corporation (EFONYS), 1962 (Box 39, Folder 57)
- Foreign Trade I, 1957-66 (Box 39, Folder 58)
- Foreign Trade II, 1962-65 (Box 39, Folder 59)
- Operational Procedures Handbook fro the Farm Bureau Trade Development Program in Export Marketing, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Foreign Trade Meeting at Rochester, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Webb - Pomerene Act 3, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Cooperative Grange League Federation Exchange (GLF) and Export Foods, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- American Farm Bureau Federation (AFBF) Export Market Newsletter, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- American Farm Bureau Federation (AFBF) Trade Development Flash(, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Trade Development Corporation, 1961-62 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Cooperative Grange League Federation Exchange (GLF) and Frozen Apples, 1961-62 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Export and E. Vander Meulen, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Foreign Trade - Fruits and Vegetables, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Rotterdam, 1959-62 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  Photos
- Imports - Lamb, Mutton, Sheep, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Foreign Trade Meeting, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Rochester Export Meeting, September 1961 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Minutes of Meeting for Apple, Bean, and Dairy Committees, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Reports to Board of Directors by C.K. Bullock, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Market Development Committee, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- New York State Poultry, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Rochester Egg Prices, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Drafting Poultry Inspection, 1957-58 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Poultry Inspection Laws, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Poultry and Egg Promotion, 1957-59 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Poulty Committee Promotion Department to Board, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Poultry Study Committee, 1957-61 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Poultry Industry Committee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Egg Weight - Model Egg Law, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Eastern Seaboard Egg Conference, September 1964 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Poultry Study Committee Reports to Board, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Northeastern Poultry Conference, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Poultry Council Reorganization, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Poultry County Committees Meeting, May 1959 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Fletcher Plan, No date (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Poultry Marketing, Yates County, 1956-57 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Poultry Research, 1959-60 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- National Egg Council, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Egg Imports from Canada, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Mandatory Grade Labeling, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Econ-O-Crax Egg Carton, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- State Purchase - Pullet Eggs, 1959-60 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Cooperative Grange League Federation Exchange (GLF) Egg Marketing, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- New York State Poultry Industry Coordinated Effort (SPICE), 1961-66 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Poultry council, 1960-64 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Egg and Broiler Marketing Act Federal, 1959-61 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- National Turkey Marketing Act, 1958-60 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Florida Egg Laws, Est. 1957 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- State Purchase of Eggs, 1954-60 (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Salmonella, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Egg Future Trading, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Insurance History, 1952-54 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Milk Price Clippings, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- 14-Man Committee, 1942-52 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Organization Committee For Independent Cooperative Farm Bureau, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- New York State Farm Bureau Federation Minutes of Board of Directors Meetings, 1935-38 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- New York State Federation Legislative Program, 1926-38 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- New York State Farm Bureau Federation Reports of Legislative Committee, 1931-38 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations Legislative Program, 1930-38 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Summary of Legislative Happenings of Interest to Agriculture, 1929-31 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Legislative Happenings in Albany, 1928-30 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- New York State Republican and Democrat Platforms on Agriculture, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- New York State Cooperative Council Legislative Activities, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Legislative Bills, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Programs of Work, 1923-31 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Northeast Farm Foundation, Est. 1946 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Milk Production and Consumption, Est. 1931-32 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Dairy Farm Mastitis Prevention and Control, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- New York Farm Bureau Various Dairy Documents, 1928-1934 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Dairy Abortion, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Farm Related Newsclippings I, 1956-57 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Farm Related News Clippings II, 1956-57 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Reports of Proceedings of Tax Conference, February 5-6, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  (notes field if needed)
- New York State Farm Bureau Federation Minutes of Board of Directors, Jaunary 13, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Organization and Extension of Farm Bureau I, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Organization and Extension of Farm Bureau II, 1954-60 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- New Farm Bureau, No Date (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Edward A. O'Neal and LaGuardia, 1943 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- American Farm Bureau Federation Reaffirmation of Pronouncements, No Date (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Taxes, Roads, and Highways, 1928-45 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Monetary Policy, No Date (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Constitution of State of New York, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Documents, 1939-54 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Legislation - Farm Bureau Conference Board, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- The Nation's Agriculture, 1935-67 (Box 43)
  Issues from September 1935 to February 1967, published by the American Farm Bureau Federation
- Bureau Farmer: The Voice of Organized Agriculture, 1934-35 (Box 43)
  Issues from January 1934 to December 1935
- Photo and Backing of S. L. Strivings, No Date (Box 44)
- Bureau Farmer, New York Edition, July 1927 - December 1928, 1927-28 (Box 44)
  Issues of the Bureau Farmer collected in hard cover binding
- Bureau Farmer, New York Edition, January 1929 - December 1929, 1929 (Box 44)
- Bureau Farmer, New York Edition, January 1930 - December 1930, 1930 (Box 44)
- Bureau Farmer, New York Edition, January 1931 - December 1931, 1931 (Box 44)
- Bureau Farmer, New York Edition, January 1932 - December 1932, 1932 (Box 44)
- Bureau Farmer, New York Edition, January 1933 - December 1933, 1933 (Box 44)
- Dairy Update, 1981-83 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  1981 Milk Facts, Procedures for Vehicle Routing Problems With An Application to Milk Assembly in New York by J.M. Schulster, J.E. Pratt ad A.M. Novakovic, Department of Agriculture, policies, negotiations, letters, testimonies, figures, statistics, legislature
- Community Nutrition Institute, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  Petition denial for a hearing on reconstituted milk pricing, letter to the president, Some Questions About and Consequences of Deregulating Reconstituted Milk by Andrew Novakovic, Petition by Community Nutrition Institute, Zy Weinberg, Deborah Harrell, Dr. Ralph Desmarais, Joseph Oberweis
- Commodity - Dairy, 1980-82 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  New York Dairy Herd Improvment Cooperative Inc., Spot Milk Cooperative Sales Desk Analysis of Proposed Solution for Richard McGuire, President, N.Y.F.B. by Fran Robbins
- Dairy 1980-82, 1980-82 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Child Nutrition Act, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Senate Documents Regarding Dairy in New York, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  Senator Cook
- Milk Strike - New York City, 1979-80 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Agriculture and Markets - 1981 Legislation, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Agricultural Districts - Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1975-83 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  Farmland Preservation Alternatives in Semi-Suburban Areas by William R. Bryant, Saving Our Farmlands, How to Create an Agricultural District: A Guide for Interested Landowners, Agricultural Districts Review Manual
- Cornell University Soil and Water Conservation Committee, 1975-76 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Farmland Inventory Soil Conservation Service, July 1975 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  Minutes of Meeting
- Land Inventory and Monitoring Soil Conservation Service, October 1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  Memorandum
- Soil and Water Conservation, State Soil and Water Conservation Committee, 1976-78 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- New York Farm Bureau Public Affairs and State Departments, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Unincorporated Business - Department of Taxation in State Departments, 1972-74 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- New York Farm Bureau Public Affairs, State Departments, Refund Forms and Taxation, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Sales Tax - Farm Trucks, Department of Taxation, State Departments, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Sales and Use Tax-Motor Fuel (Department of Taxation and Finance), 1982 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Department of Taxation, 1972-74 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  Letters, Booklet No.3: New York State and Local Sales Tax Information
- Rural Affairs Cabinet State Departments, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- New York Farm Bureau Public Affairs State Departments - Local Government, 1969-71 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Line Fence Law - Office of Local Government, 1969-72 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Milk Trucks - New York Farm Bureau Public Affairs Dept and Department of Health, No Date (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Equalization and Assessment, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Automobile Insurance - New York State Insurance Department, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Insurance - Non-Renewal of Automobile Liability Policy, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Insurance - Domestic Stock Insurer (State Department's), 1981 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Insurance - New York Farm Bureau Public Affairs and State Departments, 1971-77 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Agricultural Land Values - Department of Equalization and Assessment, 1968-82 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Assessment of Agricultural Lands - New York State Department of Equalization and Assessment, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Farmland Assessment Blanks- Department of Equalization and Assessment, No Date (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Real Property Tax Law - Department of Equalization and Assessment, 1977-78 (Box 45, Folder 32)
- Rural Affairs Council (Agriculture and Markets), 1979-80 (Box 45, Folder 33)
- Lettuce Branding Law - New York Public Affairs Department and the Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 34)
- Maple Sugarhouse License - Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 35)
- Milk Testing Rules - Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 36)
- Trespass Laws - New York Farm Bureau Public Affairs Department and the Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1971-72 (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Emergency Operations - New York Farm Bureau Public Affairs Department and the Department of AGriculture and Markets, No Date (Box 45, Folder 38)
- Fences, Strays, Pounds - Department of Agriculture and Markets, April 1973 (Box 45, Folder 39)
- Division of Weights and Measures - Department of Ag and Markets, No Date (Box 45, Folder 40)
- Dug Water Wells - Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 41)
- Commission Merchants - Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 42)
- Division of Milk Control, 1969-77 (Box 45, Folder 43)
- Cherry Marketing Order, No Date (Box 45, Folder 44)
- Cereal Leaf Beetle Quarantine, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 45)
- Budget, No Date (Box 45, Folder 46)
- Agricultural Resources Commission, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 47)
- Apple Marketing Orders, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 48)
- Agricultural District Applications, 1970-72 (Box 45, Folder 49)
- Agricultural Districts, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 50)
- Proposed Rule Making, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 51)
- Potato Research and Promotion Act, 1971-72 (Box 45, Folder 52)
- Meat Inspection Regulations, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 53)
- Packers and Stockyards Act, 1971-74 (Box 45, Folder 54)
- Milk Prices, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 55)
- Food Stamps, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 56)
- Flanigan Report, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 57)
- Consumer and Marketing Service, 1972-77 (Box 45, Folder 58)
- Cherry Marketing Orders, No Date (Box 45, Folder 59)
- Cereal Leaf Beetle, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 60)
- Apple Purchase, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 61)
- Niagara Frontier Milk, 1978-81 (Box 45, Folder 62)
  Cheese... A Challenge for Dairy Industry Action by American Dairy Association, Niagara Frontier Milk Marketing Area 1978-80, 1985 Revisited - The Future of New York Agriculture, Sales of Milk, Skim Milk and Milk Drinks in the Niagara Milk Marketing Area
- Dairy 1981, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 63)
- Property Taxation, Agricultural Value Assessments, 1976-83 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Soil and Water Conservation, No Date (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Soil Classification, Around 1981 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Forest Conservation, 1978-81 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Sludge - Plattsburgh Material and Meeting, August 1982 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Sludge I, 1980-83 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Sludge II, 1979-84 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Office of Emergency Preparedness - Federal Disaster Assistance Program, 1970-72 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Power Commission, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Office of Economic Opportunity, 1972-73 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Project Reach - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  Newspaper clipping
- Crime Prevention Program, No Date (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Poultry Farms Waste Disposal - United States Department of Justice, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Assessment for Inheritance Tax - IRS, October 1972 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Estate Taxes - IRS, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Truck Highway Use Tax - IRS, 1973-75 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Flood Insurance - United States Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1972-77 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- DES (diethylstilbestrol) - Food and Drug Administration, April 1974 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Food and Drug Administration, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- FDA Fact Sheet, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Federal Land Bank System, November 1970 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Farmers Home Administration Farm Labor Housing Legislation 1970, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Farmers Home Administration, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Cost of Living Council, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- R. P. Story Milk Marketing, Around 1969 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Air Quality, 1978-83 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Water Rights, 1975-78 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Pollutant Discharge Elimination System (NPDES) Permits, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Water Resources, 1978-83 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Upper Wallkill River Flood Control, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Pure Water Act of 1970 - Environmental Protection Agency, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Water Protection Control Act of 1972 - Environmental Protection Agency, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Pollutant Discharge Elimination System - Environmental Protection Agency, 1973-75 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Permit Program - Point Source Discharge - Environmental Protection Agency, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- Environmental Protection Agency (General), 1978 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Fuel and Fuel Additives - Environmental Protection Agency, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 36)
- Feedlot Run-Off, 1973-74 (Box 46, Folder 37)
- New York Farm Bureau Public Affairs Dept and Federal Agencies - Environmental Protection Agency, 1973-77 (Box 46, Folder 38)
- Clean Water Act of 1972 - Environmental Protection Agency, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 39)
- Clean Air Act - Environmental Protection Agency, 1971-73 (Box 46, Folder 40)
- Directions Through Region II: A Guide to Units Within the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency's Region II Office, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 41)
- Auto Emission Standards - Environmental Protection Agency, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 42)
- Railroads, 1974-75 (Box 46, Folder 43)
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 1974-77 (Box 46, Folder 44)
- Environmental Regulation, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 45)
- Environmental Protection Agency, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 46)
- Pollution, 1979-74 (Box 46, Folder 47)
- Documents Regarding Environmental Issues, 1979-84 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  Pesticides, New York Environmental Voter's Guide, Sierra Club, soil conservation, water resources, technology, environmentalism
- Land Use Planning, 1974-77 (Box 46, Folder 49)
- Family Farms - Rural Development, 1978-79 (Box 46, Folder 50)
- Abandoned Orchards, 1975-78 (Box 46, Folder 51)
- Property Taxation - Agricultural Value Assessment, 1978-80 (Box 46, Folder 52)
- Property Taxation Revaluation, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  Property Record Card for Commercial Farms in New York State and Directions for Use by William H. King, Cornell University
- Property Taxation - Agricultural Use Value, 1976-80 (Box 46, Folder 54)
- Property Taxation - Preservation of Farmland, 1974-80 (Box 46, Folder 55)
- Congressional Record, Volume 120, No. 61-66, May 2-13, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Water, 1975-77 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Water Pollution - Department of Interior, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Water Rights - Agriculture Department, No Date (Box 47, Folder 4)
  Water Rights Under Riparian and Appropriation Doctrines
- Soil Conservation Service, 1974-81 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Assessing Prime and Unique Farmland - Department of Agricultural Soil Conservation Service, 1975-79 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Rural Clean Water, 1978-79 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Army Corps of Engineers - Rivers and Harbors Act of 1899, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Army Corps of Engineers - Tocks Island Dam, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Army Corps of Engineers - Refuse Act of 1899, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Army Corps of Engineers - Mud Creek Project - Steuben Co., September 1973 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Army Corps Engineers, 1970-72 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Statistical Reporting Service, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Use of Diethylstilbestrol, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Wheat and Feed Grains, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- United States Department of Agriculture, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Soybean Embargo, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Regulation of Eggs, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Secretary Butz, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Rural Environmental Assistance Program, 1973-74 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Flood, 1973-77 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Drinking Water Supplies - State Department of Health, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Water Well Drillers, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Water Quality Standards, 1976-78 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Tug Hill Commission, 1976-77 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Thermal Pollution, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Stream Protection, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Stream Classification, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Resource Material, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Stack Omissions, No Date (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Soil and Water Conservation Districts, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Sanitary Code - Landfills, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Marine Fisheries Management Program, 1977-78 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Marine Sanctuary Act, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Open Burning Permits, 1977-81 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- Stream Protection, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 36)
- Stream Preservation, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 37)
- Stream Disturbance, 1975-76 (Box 47, Folder 38)
- Stream Classification, 1973-74 (Box 47, Folder 39)
- Returnable Beverage Containers, 1975-79 (Box 47, Folder 40)
- Returnable Bottles, 1977-79 (Box 47, Folder 41)
- Groveland Flats, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 42)
- Mined Land Reclamation Law, No Date (Box 47, Folder 43)
- Paprocki Case, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 44)
- Noise Control, 1972-73 (Box 47, Folder 45)
- Mountain Pride Farms, 1974-76 (Box 47, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous - Department of Environmental Conservation, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 47)
- Landfills - Department of Environmental Conservation, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 48)
- Hearing - June 21, 1972, June 21, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 49)
- Fuel Standards, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 50)
- Forest Land Taxation, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 51)
- Adirondack Park Agency, 1973-76 (Box 47, Folder 52)
- Farmer Identified Environmental Issues (DEC), 1981 (Box 47, Folder 53)
- Construction in Flood Plain Areas, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 54)
- Codes, Rules and Regulations, 1972-76 (Box 47, Folder 55)
- Catskill Study Commission, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 56)
- Black River Valley Flats, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 57)
- Animal Waste Disposal, 1972-73 (Box 47, Folder 58)
- Agricultural Advisory Council (DEC), 1980 (Box 47, Folder 59)
- Air Pollution, 1971-74 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Farm Bureau Member Recruits, 1923-62 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  Includes a map of Green County New York
- Copies of Apple Marketing Orders, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- A History of Agricultural Extension Work in the United States 1785-1923, No Date (Box 48, Folder 4)
  By Alfred Charles True, pages 158-171
- Marketing Agreements in Effects, 1959-61 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Marketing Agent Act Award 1958-59, 1958-59 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- State Act - Marketing Orders, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Marketing Order Information, 1952-61 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Marketing Agreements and Orders, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Farmers and Political Involvement, No Date (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Political Education and Action Program, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- PACA, 1950-59 (Box 48, Folder 12)